Guide to the Evan Rupert Nash Collection, 1827-1945
Department of Special Collections
- Additions to Nash Family Collection
  - Printed Material (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - 2. [ The Circular] Number 2, July 25. Printed letter of Edwin Nash to Dear Friends Written July 2, 1864.
    - 3. Evening Varieties, No. 3, Feb. 3, 1865,a printed broadside program.
    - 4. Noyes, Hilda H., The Development of Useful Citizenship, reprint from Journal of Heredity, vol. XI, no. 2, Washington D. C., February 1920, p. 88-91.
    - 5. Noyes, Hilda Herrick and George Wallingford Noyes, The Oneida Community Experiment in Stirpiculture, reprinted from Eugenics, Genetics and the Family, vol I, 1923, p. 374-386.
    - 6. Noyes, John Humphrey, Male Continence, Oneida, N. Y., Oneida Community, 1872.
    - 7. Oneida Community, By-laws of the Oneida Community Limited, Together With An Act to Provide for the Organization and Regulation of Certain Business Corporations., Passed by the Legislature of New York, June 21, 1875, Community, N. Y., Oneida Community Limited, 1881.
    - 8. Oneida Community, Handbook of the Oneida Community; Containing a Brief Sketch of Its Present Condition, Internal Economy, And Leading Principles, No. 2, Oneida Community, N. Y., 1871.
    - 9. Oneida Community, 1848-1901.
    - 10. Parkhurst, Henry M., Diana: or, The Secret of a Happy Married Life. A Pyscho-physiological Essay on Sexual Relations, reprinted from the Civil Forum, September, 1916.